

Product Designer

Product Designer with a strong background in Digital Marketing and Web Development, including an intensive web development bootcamp that provided me with a broad and integrated view of the digital creation process. With over 10 years of experience in strategic digital planning and now focused on UX/UI Design, I have skills in conducting usability research, developing wireframes and interactive prototypes, and collaborating with development teams to ensure the effective implementation of user-centered interfaces. My technical and creative background allows me to create digital solutions that meet both business needs and user expectations.

Contacts You can find me at 🔗 Languages

E-mail: babs.agra@gmail.com <u>LinkedIn</u> <u>Website</u> Portuguese | Native

Phone: +351 912592474 <u>Behance</u> English | Fluent

EDUCATION

AUG 2021 - SEP 2024 OUT 2022 - DEZ 2022 AUG 2009 - AUG 2014

Master in New Media and Web PracticesWeb Development BootcampBachelor of Arts in CommunicationsNova University LisbonIronhack LisbonFACHA - Rio de Janeiro, BR

WORK EXPERIENCE

JUL 2022 - SEP 2024 Freelance Digital Specialist - Azuli

At Azuli, I have assembled a diverse portfolio of freelance work, specializing in branding, social media content, and web development. Working with companies such as:

• Prado Imóveis Litoral; Prado Decor; Ytech.io; Universidade Nova de Lisboa, Drama Clube.

AUG 2021 - SET 2022 Social Media Manager - Papori Interactive Marketing Lisbon, PT

- Made innovative and captivating social media plans (contents, ideas, promotions);
- Developed visual and interactive design projects using tools such as Photoshop, Figma, and Canva, ensuring brand consistency and user engagement;
- Let the creation of content strategies that balanced user needs with marketing objectives resulting in increased public satisfaction and engagement;
- Managing multiple responsibilities as the primary marketing professional within the team;
- Develop and maintain a consistent brand voice across all marketing channels;
- Track campaigns and reports of data.

DEC 2011 - JAN 2019 Marketing Coordinator - Woohoo Channel
Rio de Janeiro, BR

- Social media management resulting in an increase of **2M followers**. development of relevance and credibility with the audience (Facebook, Instagram, Twitter and LinkedIn);
- Reports and content performance and recommending strategy changes based on data;
- Coordination on multiple projects simultaneously, ensuring good communication and work-flow between multiple engagement teams;
- Planning and executing campaigns to achieve key performance indicators.

KEY SKILLS

Photoshop	InDesign	Premiere	Wordpress	Javascript
Illustrator	Figma	HTML & CSS	Bootstrap	React